let quizzData = [

    {
        name: 'English',
        quizzes: [
            {
                question: "Missy said hello ____ of everyone in her group of friends.",
                answer: [
                    "The most cheerfully",
                    "The cheerfulliest",
                    "The more cheerfully",
                    "The cheerfullier"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "The most cheerfully"
            },
            {
                question: "Several children in the class are ____, but Harriet is the ____ by far.",
                answer: [
                    "Clever/ more cleverest",
                    "Clever/ cleverest",
                    "Clever/ most cleverest",
                    "Clever/ more cleverer"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Clever/ cleverest"
            },
            {
                question: "Karen walked ____ to the bus stop than Sally.",
                answer: [
                    "Briskliest",
                    "Brisklier",
                    "More briskly",
                    "Most briskly"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "More briskly"
            },
            {
                question: "I gave my bike a wash and now it looks ____.",
                answer: [
                    "Gooder",
                    "Better",
                    "More good",
                    "Best"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Better"
            },
            {
                question: "A ballet dancer usually dances ____ than me.",
                answer: [
                    "More gracefully",
                    "Most gracefully",
                    "Gracefullier",
                    "Gracefulliest"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "More gracefully"
            },
            {
                question: "Paul has two big trees in his back garden, but the oak tree is ____ the ash tree.",
                answer: [
                    "The more taller",
                    "The most tallest",
                    "Taller than",
                    "Tallest"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Taller than"
            },
            {
                question: "The Missouri river is ____ river in the USA, but the river Nile is ____ it.",
                answer: [
                    "The longest/ longer than",
                    "The longest/ longest than",
                    "The long/ longer than",
                    "The longer/ the longer than"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "The longest/ longer than"
            },
            {
                question: "Cheetahs may run ____ than horses, but the horses run ____ across a field of every animal.",
                answer: [
                    "The most swiftly/ more beautifully",
                    "Swiftly/ more beautifully",
                    "The swiftliest/ the beautifullier",
                    "More swiftly/ the most beautifully"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "More swiftly/ the most beautifully"
            },
            {
                question: "Dave would like a ____ sugar in his tea; Peter would like ____ sugar than Dave, and Bill would like ____ sugar of all.",
                answer: [
                    "Little/ less/ the least",
                    "Little/ least/ less",
                    "Less/ Little/ least",
                    "Least/ less/ little"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Little/ less/ the least"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adjectives in the following sentence.
                The road comprised large houses and a tiny shop.`,
                answer: [
                    "Comprised",
                    "Houses/ shop",
                    "Large/ tiny",
                    "Road/ large"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Large/ tiny"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adjectives in the following sentence.
                The old book had lost its original cover long ago.`,
                answer: [
                    "Book/ cover",
                    "Lost/ long",
                    "Old/ original",
                    "The/ its"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Old/ original"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adjectives in the following sentence.
                The long transporter delivered the new car today.`,
                answer: [
                    "Delivered/ today",
                    "Long/ new",
                    "The/ the",
                    "Transporter/ car"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Long/ new"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adjectives in the following sentence.
                This bag is heavy but that bag is light.`,
                answer: [
                    "Bag/ bag",
                    "Heavy/ light",
                    "Is/ is",
                    "This/ that"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Heavy/ light"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adjectives in the following sentence.
                The quick brown fox jumped over the slow white dog.`,
                answer: [
                    "Jumped/ over/ the/ dog",
                    "Quick/ brown/ slow/ white",
                    "The/ fox/ the/ dog",
                    "The/ jumped/ over/ the"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Quick/ brown/ slow/ white"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the atonym for the following word.
                                       Empty`,
                answer: [
                    "Drained",
                    "Full",
                    "Poured out",
                    "Vacant"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Full"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the atonym for the following word.
                                       Stale`,
                answer: [
                    "Fresh",
                    "Kept too long",
                    "Musty",
                    "Old"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Fresh"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the atonym for the following word.
                                       Shout`,
                answer: [
                    "Cry",
                    "Scream",
                    "Shriek",
                    "Whisper"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Whisper"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the atonym for the following word.
                                       Few`,
                answer: [
                    "A minority",
                    "A small number",
                    "Many",
                    "Not many"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Many"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the atonym for the following word.
                                       Bright`,
                answer: [
                    "Dull",
                    "Radiant",
                    "Shining",
                    "Sparkling"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Dull"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the atonym for the following word.
                                       Shut`,
                answer: [
                    "Barred",
                    "Closed",
                    "Fastened",
                    "Open"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Open"
            },
            {
                question: "Select the correct capital letters in the following sentence.",
                answer: [
                    "red sky means good weather it will be sunny tomorrow",
                    "Red sky means good weather. it will be sunny tomorrow",
                    "Red sky means good weather. it will be sunny tomorrow.",
                    "Red sky means good weather. It will be sunny tomorrow."
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Red sky means good weather. It will be sunny tomorrow."
            },
            {
                question: "Select the correct capital letters in the following sentence.",
                answer: [
                    "where is the blue book is it in the pile on the table?",
                    "where is the blue book. is it in the pile on the table.",
                    "Where is the blue book? Is it in the pile on the table?",
                    "Where is the blue book? is it in the pile on the table?"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Where is the blue book? Is it in the pile on the table?"
            },
            {
                question: "Select the correct capital letters in the following sentence.",
                answer: [
                    "tom played the Piano well kate Forgot her music.",
                    "tom played the piano well kate forgot her music.",
                    "Tom played the piano well. Kate forgot her music.",
                    "Tom played the Piano well. Kate forgot her Music."
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Tom played the piano well. Kate forgot her music."
            },
            {
                question: "Select the correct capital letters in the following sentence.",
                answer: [
                    "Capital letters are useful do you use them correctly?",
                    "Capital letters are useful. Do you use them correctly?",
                    "capital letters are useful. Do you use them correctly?",
                    "capital letters are useful. do you use them correctly?"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Capital letters are useful. Do you use them correctly?"
            },
            {
                question: "Select the correct capital letters in the following sentence.",
                answer: [
                    "where is your first aid kit? Did you leave it in the car",
                    "where is your first aid kit? Did you leave it in the car",
                    "Where is your first aid kit? Did you leave it in the car?",
                    "Where is your first aid kit? did you leave it in the car?"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Where is your first aid kit? Did you leave it in the car?"
            },
            {
                question: "Select the correct capital letters in the following sentence.",
                answer: [
                    "the door is freshly painted don't touch it",
                    "the door is freshly painted Don't touch it.",
                    "The door is freshly painted. don't touch it",
                    "The door is freshly painted. Don't touch it."
                ],
                trueAnswer: "The door is freshly painted. Don't touch it."
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adverbs in the following sentence.
                Use words effectively to produce interesting writing.`,
                answer: [
                    "Words",
                    "Interesting writing",
                    "Use",
                    "Effectively"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Effectively"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adverbs in the following sentence.
                Many interesting adverbs enhance writing appropriately.`,
                answer: [
                    "Appropriately",
                    "Interesting ",
                    "Enhance",
                    "Writing"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Appropriately"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adverbs in the following sentence.
                He ran quickly last season but slowly this season.`,
                answer: [
                    "Last season/ this season",
                    "Last/ this ",
                    "Quickly/ slowly",
                    "Slowly/ season"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Quickly/ slowly"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adverbs in the following sentence.
                He started slowly then ran quickly and finished early.`,
                answer: [
                    "Slowly/ quickly/ early",
                    "Started/ ran/ finished",
                    "He/ then/ and",
                    "Slowly/ quickly/ finished"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Slowly/ quickly/ early"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the adverbs in the following sentence.
                Produce interesting writing consistently using adverbs.`,
                answer: [
                    "Interesting writing",
                    "Consistently",
                    "Using adverbs",
                    "Produce"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Consistently"
            },
            {
                question: `Choose the best answer for the following sentence.
                The appropriate work of teacher is___________?`,
                answer: [
                    "To organize teaching work",
                    "To evaluate the students",
                    "To deliver lecture in class",
                    "All above"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "All above"
            },
            {
                question: `Choose the best answer for the following sentence.
                Dylan’s lucky number is ___________`,
                answer: [
                    "Tree",
                    "These",
                    "Three",
                    "Free"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Free"
            },
            {
                question: `Choose the best answer for the following sentence.
                The___________had to sweep up all the leaves.`,
                answer: [
                    "Teacher",
                    "Plumber",
                    "Doctor",
                    "Gardener"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Gardener"
            },
            {
                question: `Choose the best answer for the following sentence.
                The more parts of your brain you use, the more likely you are to __________ information.`,
                answer: [
                    "Miss",
                    "Use",
                    "Retain",
                    "Misuse"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Retain"
            },
            {
                question: `Choose the best answer for the following sentence.
                They all lived __________ ever after.`,
                answer: [
                    "Hardly",
                    "Happily",
                    "Happiest",
                    "Poor"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "happily"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the synonyms for the following word.
                                       Start`,
                answer: [
                    "Begin",
                    "End",
                    "Finish",
                    "Forbid"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Begin"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the synonyms for the following word.
                                       Carefully`,
                answer: [
                    "Dangerously",
                    "Continuously",
                    "Cautiously",
                    "Previously"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Cautiously"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the synonyms for the following word.
                                       Carefully`,
                answer: [
                    "Dangerously",
                    "Continuously",
                    "Cautiously",
                    "Previously"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Cautiously"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the synonyms for the following word.
                                       Construct`,
                answer: [
                    "Demolish",
                    "Hinder",
                    "Prevent",
                    "Build up"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Build up"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the synonyms for the following word.
                                       Fed up with`,
                answer: [
                    "Come up with",
                    "Catch up with",
                    "Bored with",
                    "Put up with"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Bored with"
            },
            {
                question: `Select the synonyms for the following word.
                                       Obsolete`,
                answer: [
                    "Outdated",
                    "Fashionable",
                    "New",
                    "Present"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Outdated"
            },
            {
                question: "'I can't breathe because my nose is blocked.' Which word is a verb?",
                answer: [
                    "Breath",
                    "Nose",
                    "Can't",
                    "Because"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Breath."
            },
            {
                question: "'I enjoy tennis, football and playing snooker.' How many verbs are in that sentence?",
                answer: [
                    "4",
                    "2",
                    "3",
                    "1"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "2"
            },
            {
                question: "'I will not stand when I'm told to.' - which word is the verb?",
                answer: [
                    "Will",
                    "Not",
                    "When",
                    "Told"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Told"
            },
            {
                question: "Which sentence doesn't contain a verb?",
                answer: [
                    "I enjoy eating in restaurants.",
                    "There would be no plants, no animals and no human beings",
                    "All the living things on Earth get their energy from the Sun for their survival",
                    "The Solar System consists of the Sun, Moon, Planets, comets, meteoroids and asteroids"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "There would be no plants, no animals and no human beings"
            },
            {
                question: "Mark prefers playing badminton rather than swimming. -How many verbs are in that sentence?",
                answer: [
                    "1",
                    "4",
                    "2",
                    "3"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "3"
            },
            {
                question: "Which sentence doesn't contain a verb?",
                answer: [
                    "A specific vaccine for humans effective in preventing Corona virus is not yet readily available.",
                    "The post office is a very important government institution.",
                    "I feel pity seeing the beggar but I can’t help it I can only pray to God to help the beggar to earn his livelihood.",
                    "The doctor is a person who looks after the sick people and prescribes medicines so that the patient recovers fast."
                ],
                trueAnswer: "The post office is a very important government institution."
            },
            {
                question: `Find the mistake in the following sentence.
                The doctor which we met in France has just sent us a greeting card.`,
                answer: [
                    "Which",
                    "Has",
                    "Met",
                    "France."
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Which"
            },
            {
                question: `Find the mistake in the following sentence.
                We cancelled our camping trip because of it rained heavily.`,
                answer: [
                    "Cancelled",
                    "Heavily",
                    "Because of",
                    "Camping."
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Because of"
            },
            {
                question: `Find the mistake in the following sentence.
                The man with whom we speak in the park this morning is my teacher.`,
                answer: [
                    "Speak",
                    "With whom",
                    "Is",
                    "The"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Speak"
            },
            {
                question: `Find the mistake in the following sentence.
                It was not easy for us getting tickets for the concert.`,
                answer: [
                    "It",
                    "For",
                    "Getting",
                    "The"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Getting"
            },
            {
                question: `Find the mistake in the following sentence.
               I wish all the children in the world don't have to live in poverty any longer.`,
                answer: [
                    "Wish",
                    "Don't have to",
                    "Any longer",
                    "Poverty"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Don't have to"
            },
            {
                question: `Find the mistake in the following sentence.
               Mike has not eaten some meat since he got advice from his doctor.`,
                answer: [
                    "Eaten",
                    "Some",
                    "Advice",
                    "Since"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Some"
            },
            {
                question: `Find the mistake in the following sentence.
               Linda asked Tom whether he had gone to Audrey's birthday party last night.`,
                answer: [
                    "Had gone",
                    "Whether",
                    "Last night",
                    "Birthday"
                ],
                trueAnswer: "Last night"
            },
        ]
    }
]